That friends how are they, you submit,
you people will ask once again welcome to
our YouTube channel in today's
video we are going to talk about
how to apply for subscribing to the registration certificate like you will
tell you something in this video so stay tuned
you are with us tell
Ajay
that nowadays friends there is a
lot of problem in getting the IS certificate in the last period, so the
IA exam is not being conducted
if you
try to give the ABS exam in some other way
or privately you go directly to the website
of Indian Institute of Banking Finance and
if you create an account
from here the account is not being created
and at some centers the exam is also
not being conducted and the festival of Aadhar there
IABF means it is very
important for you to have it and for this you
need IS very difficult at this
time because all the jewels are connected to each other
so friends in today's video we will tell you
how to apply for the IF certificate and
how you will have to give the exam in this last period
Uda Prasiddh will tell you that you should
watch the full video from the beginning till the end,
if you watch the video even a little bit or if you
watch the video by doing the next process even a little bit, then your entire exam will be
wasted and
you will be left with no name, so let's
start by subscribing so that
after coming to the search here,
you have to like subscribe here, then
here banking Indian Institute
of Banking and Finance will be done,
we have to click on it, then it will
open, this for friends please
subscribe button has been done, from here
you have to enter your name, come
here subscribe, here
you have to subscribe the pin code channel, if you have
subscribed specifically in the subscription, then
you are subscribed here, here
you can give a
lot, if you want you can give the
phone number, you have to see it here, you have to give the Aadhar card,
here you have to put your photograph
and signature,
okay, here select ID proof,
in ID proof you can put the driving license,
if you do that subscribe
Video plz subscribe  Here and here
you must subscribe to click here and
subscribe and the photo
is 01 or its dimension should be nearby
okay you can set it to small you can set the
dimension of any photo by
opening it a little you can set the tension
if you have no problem
in setting the time then you can comment me I will
tell you how to fix the dimension by
making a video and collection okay then after this
add come down here here
you have to select the medium in
English because in the medium you want to give that
then here you have to
give the center here enter the name here
before clicking you have to select the district
okay whatever your
district you have to choose what will happen with this
friends whatever district you use
then all the centers conducting the
exam of that district only in that district will
open in front of you
okay
now here is a very important
topic important point it has to be
modern if you mix this then
all your these basic  Keep the knowledge, okay, so
here the option of sisters was given,
you have to click on the option given, so here
in some options the names of some centers will
open here, okay friends,
here as soon as you
move your mouse pointer over any center,
a separate message will be shown here, all the
details of the entire center will be
shown there, the center address, the
contact number of the center will appear flat here, okay
friends, and here you can see that the
mobile number has been sent on the screen,
before selecting the center,
friends, contact on this mobile number here, you have to
talk that I
want to give the IVF exam, that you are
conducting it at this time
and which date do I have to choose, the date is
okay, whether the time is available, you have to select the
hint, we have talked a bit, okay,
if it says that it is
for us, then only you click on the center, otherwise
now you can talk to another center, in
this way, try this on almost all the Adarsh ​​​​Aadhaar centers here.
Whichever exam
we ask you to conduct, you have to select their center
and ask them for the date and time,
you have to select the same time, okay
friends, you will do this much and
you have to apply in this way, okay then your
exam will be conducted and you will easily
get your ABS certificate, you can get it by logging
in, it is difficult, as soon as
you fill this form, then
send a or next on your mail ID,
you will get its admit card and
whatever your date is, you can go to the state and submit
your contribution, after this there is
an option given here, this is crib
required, if you need any special service
then you can click here, leave
it as no, after this by
clicking the captcha you have to cut the proceed for
payment,
you have to cut the payment only when the
center people say yes to you
for conducting the exam, if we ask you for the
date, then you have to select the date and set the
time, in which way
you will be
able to see the exam by going to it, so in this way you  You can make
your IA certificate very easily
during long gown days, so
friends, mix this used oil
or if you liked the video then please
like the video, if you
want to help any of your friends,
please share the video with us friends and if you are visiting the
channel for the first time then subscribe to the channel
because I give you similar
CAC and DAX related videos every day, so till then
bye-bye with my video